Kar do
[music]
Loot
Hello Vivah Mrityu Agarwal Welcome and welcome
back to my YouTube channel and train
Before starting today's video, if you have
n't subscribed to my channel, please
subscribe to my channel and
press the bell icon so that
you get the notification of every upcoming video first So
let's start its video
that now there will be insurance for eclipse in the country, yes there will be
insurance for eclipse in the country
ICICI Lombard has launched a
policy for operators, now those who default on loans will be
able to avail insurance cover for this
ICICI Lombard, the largest general insurance company in the private sector, has launched
a special comprehensive insurance plan for zone operators. It will
cover theft of aircraft during theft or any damage caused to it, such as damage to its camera equipment. It will
also cover third party liability. As per the DGCA
directive, currently only vehicles
cannot go inside the virus-affected areas
but it can be used for
sanitization, exploitation and other types of surveillance in virus-affected areas. The
insurance policy is of the
Directorate General of Civil Aviation and the
Ministry of Civil Aviation MCA
Commercial use of drones will be approved by the government. Such
operators can avail both liability cover and liability cover.
16 types of risks will be covered.
Under the policy, theft, disappearance or
accidental damage to the drone will be covered.
Breakage and subsequent defects are
not covered.
Losses due to non-compliance with DDCA directives are also not covered.
Accidental damage to equipment and equipment curve uploads is also covered.
This insurance
policy covers bodily injury caused during drone operation in India and due to
accidents related to it.
If the operator has insurance
cover, third party cover is also available.
Medical insurance
cover is also available for the operator. This includes
hospitalization due to bodily injury arising from flying the covered drone.
Accidental bodily
injury and property damage due to the drone will
also be covered. Loan insurance can also be availed online.
Sanjay Dutta of ICICI Lombard, its company, says that
Heroin has
seen tremendous growth potential in recent times.
Due to its increasing use by both commercial and civilian sectors, the
losses incurred due to it are less.  Insurance cover has become necessary for this
wherever the company has
launched a product related to Ronne Soren, this
Orange will also be available online, that's all for today's video,
if you liked the video then do
like, comment and share the video,
thank you and it is done.